https://www.graphon.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
GraphOn is Committed to Protecting your Personal Information
Personal Information
GraphOn requires personal information in order to provide licenses, technical support, and product notification services, as outlined in our Support Contract and License Agreement, with the sole purpose of supporting the ongoing operation and use of GO-Global. GraphOn does not share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties.
Personal information for prospects and licensed end-users (customers) is often provided to GraphOn through an authorized channel partner (Distributors, Resellers, ISV partners, HSP partners, and OEM partners). GraphOn channel partners are not required or authorized to collect any personal information other than outlined in this policy.
Prospects. The personal information required by GraphOn for a prospect contact includes name, email address, company name, and country location.
Customers. The personal information required by GraphOn for a customer contact includes name, email address, company name, company address, and country location. To confirm eligibility for certain price models, GraphOn may also require the customer to provide a company website URL and telephone number.
Channel Partner. The personal information required by GraphOn for a channel partner contact includes name, email address, company name, company address, country location, company website URL, and telephone number.
GraphOn services, documentation, and downloads are accessible in the GraphOn Customer Portal, which requires logon credentials using an email address as the contact identifier in order to establish a GraphOn account. Passwords are encrypted and no additional personal information, other than outlined above, and with the exception of Credit Card Orders, is requested or required in order to access and utilize the Customer Portal.
Personal Information Collection Points
The following is a list and description of each point on our website or in our Customer Portal where personal information is either collected by GraphOn, or personal information on file is required to utilize certain services or functions.
Contact Us
This page is used for visitors to submit general inquiries about GraphOn or GO-Global. The visitor is required to input a first name, last name, company name, and email address. When submitted, this information is stored in our contact database so GraphOn can evaluate and respond via email.
Acceptance of this Privacy Policy is required.
GraphOn may forward this contact information to a GraphOn channel partner to assist with technical or commercial issues.
30-Day Free Trial
This page is used to initiate a GO-Global 30-day free trial. To activate a free trial, prospects are required to create a GraphOn account, which requires inputting a first name, last name, company name, email address, and password. When submitted, this information is stored in our contact database so GraphOn can follow up and provide assistance to the prospect during the trial period. Passwords are encrypted.
Acceptance of this Privacy Policy is required.
GraphOn may forward this contact information to a GraphOn channel partner to assist with technical or commercial issues.
Create GraphOn Account
This function is launched in two possible ways: a) when creating a GraphOn account on the Customer Portal, and b) when creating a GraphOn account in order to activate a 30-Day free trial.   Required input includes first name, last name, company name, email address, and password. When submitted, this information is stored in GraphOn’s contact database. Passwords are encrypted.
Acceptance of this Privacy Policy is required.
Lead Registration
This page is used by GraphOn channel partners to register an end-user prospect account as exclusive to a specific partner.GraphOn channel partners are required to provide the prospect’s first name, last name, company name, email address, and country. When submitted, this information is stored in GraphOn’s contact database. GraphOn may follow up with the prospect to monitor progress or status regarding GO-Global.
License Change Request
This page is used by existing licensed end-user customers to request license changes which are necessary to continue the operation of GO-Global. This form is sometimes completed by a GraphOn channel partner on behalf of the end-user customer, as a service and convenience. The form requestor may provide end-user customer email addresses to receive the revised licenses.
Emergency License Request
This page is used by existing licensed end-user customers to request an Emergency License in the event of a catastrophic server failure. The requestor email address must already exist in the GraphOn contact database, and the required input to complete this form includes first name, last name, company name, and email address. Upon completion of this process, the requestor will receive an Emergency License via email.
License Activation
This page is used by end-user customers to activate a new GO-Global license. The requestor email address is required. If provided during the order entry process or 30-day free trial process, the email address may already exist in the GraphOn contact database. If not, it will be added to the contact database. Upon completion of this process, the requestor will receive the new license file via email.
Order Forms
Order forms are used by customers and channel partners who have a direct commercial relationship with GraphOn. Generally speaking, the purchasing contact will complete the form. The required information to successfully process an order will include:
Purchasing Contact name, email address, Bill To company address, and phone number, as well as any additional email addresses the purchasing contact designates to receive a copy of the order via email.
Bill To Contact email address, as well as any additional email addresses the purchasing contact designates to receive a copy of the invoice via email.
End-User Customer Contact name, email address, and company address, as well as any additional email addresses who the purchasing contact designates to receive copies of the Activation Keys necessary for License Activation.
Any contact information which does not previously exist in the GraphOn contact database will be added as part of the processing.
Credit Card Information
GraphOn licensees and channel partners who purchase products or services directly from GraphOn have several payment options available which do not require providing additional personal information other than outlined above. GraphOn licensees and channel partners who chose to pay with a credit card will be required to provide full credit card details, including credit card number, expiration date, security code, card holder name, card billing address and country, and card phone number. Unless otherwise agreed and authorized by the card holder, GraphOn does not store credit card details on file.
Product Notifications and Marketing
GraphOn sends the following types of communications to its Contact database:
Product Notifications. These communications are targeted to end-user customers and channel partner contacts for the purpose of supporting the ongoing operations of GO-Global. These communications may include critical notices regarding security or patch releases, or may be a routine notice of availability of a new release.
License Renewal Notifications. These communications are exclusive to end-user customers and channel partners; they are sent to specific contacts, and include critical information about support contract expirations. The purpose of these communications is to assist end-user customers and channel partners to submit timely license renewals to: a) maintain support for licenses and, b) avoid reactivation fees applied when renewing expired licenses.
Product Marketing. These communications are targeted to contact database prospects who have made inquiries in the past but are not licensed end-users. These communications generally include information about GO-Global features and new releases.
Cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks your permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. Using cookies, web applications tailor their operation by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages on our website are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by allowing us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Recourse / Compliance
If you believe that the personal information we are holding is incorrect or incomplete, or if you are uncertain as to what information we are holding, or if you are receiving unwanted communications from GraphOn, please email privacy@graphon.com from the email address involved, and/or take the action you’ve requested.
Change Cookie Consent
Privacy settings
Decide which cookies you want to allow.
You can change these settings at any time. However, this can result in some functions no longer being available. For information on deleting the cookies, please consult your browser’s help function.
Learn more about the cookies we use.
With the slider, you can enable or disable different types of cookies:
Block all
Essentials
Functionality
Analytics
Advertising
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selected
This website won't:
Remember your login detailsFunctionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies.Advertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and country
This website won't:
Remember your login detailsAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies.Advertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Remember social media settingsl Functionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functions
This website won't:
Remember your login detailsAdvertising: Use information for tailored advertising with third partiesAdvertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesAdvertising: Identify device you are usingAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will:
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms, newsletter and other forms across all pagesEssential: Keep track of what you input in a shopping cartEssential: Authenticate that you are logged into your user accountEssential: Remember language version you selectedFunctionality: Remember social media settingsl Functionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Use information for tailored advertising with third partiesAdvertising: Allow you to connect to social sitesl Advertising: Identify device you are usingAdvertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website won't:
Remember your login details
Save & Close
Cookie Consent Notification
GraphOn uses "cookies" and other browser-based storage mechanisms to provide the best experience possible.  GraphOn may also use these technologies to perform analysis of your usage of our website for the purposes of optimization and further development of the site.
By clicking Accept All Cookies you agree to our use of cookies and related browser-storage technologies.  Click Privacy Policy for complete details or to change your cookie consent settings.
Accept All Cookies
Privacy Policy
